[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]
[Heo Seong-jin, Diori’s ‘Night of Counting Stars’]
Stand...
senior
Senior!
[Wham - Siren]
Ai, Mr. Ugh.
Go quickly!
[Dongju] Kim Jonghyun!
Kim Jonghyun!
[Wham - Siren]
[Devil] Oh my
Things seem to be going wrong
[Call connection tone]
[Dongju] Hey, Kim Jonghyun
Kim Jonghyun, come to your senses.
senior
[Calm music]
[Nurse] You can’t come in.
[Beep beep - ECG]
Ah, teacher, uh...
[Mansik sighs]
[Wing - Cell Phone]
[Call connection tone]
[Guidance voice] I can't answer the phone.
To the sound source...
[dark music]
[Call connection tone]
It's me
What I prepared
Please send some kids.
[People laughing]
[Man] This time, the development
Because it passes quickly
- Our region took a breather.
- [Deokgyu] Come on, have a drink, come on.
[Man] Oh, I feel reassured.
[Deokgyu] Ah...
Are you here, Mayor?
[Jooyoung sighs]
Why aren't you answering the phone?
civil servant
Well, that...
It's not that I didn't answer the phone.
Because of an urgent appointment
Hey, I heard about the situation.
Then, if you file a complaint
You have to deal with it.
I don't have time
[Deokgyu] I want to do that too
Why?
Is the money you’ve received so far not enough?
How much more can I give you? tell me
no, that's not it
what can i do
Because it's not
Wow, that
What is Minister Min?
I think you're misunderstanding
Because this isn't about money
Ah, why are you like this? Why are you like this!
Ah, what's wrong, ah, this is real
It's not about money!
[Jooyoung] ‘Ah’
'Ah'
- [Dark Music]
- Ah, ah
Oh?
Ah...
[Deokgyu’s scream]
If the complainant makes a request
I need some help
Aren't you a civil servant?
[Deokgyu] Ah!
I pay so much attention to each and every detail
I'll take care of it for you.
[Coughing]
[Cluck cluck]
[Deokgyu’s labored breathing]
[Deokgyu chuckles]
Why, is it still not enough?
[Deokgyu] No, no! Crack cack...
Then please take care of me, okay?
yes?
Uh oh
- Yes
- [Deokgyu’s cough]
- [Dark Music]
- [Wham - Siren]
[Jiseok] Inseong Coast Guard
This is Sergeant Lee Ji-seok.
I'll stop doing everything
Coast Guard?
[Korea Customs Service Employee 1]
I came from the customs office.
[Korea Customs Service Employee 2]
This is our jurisdiction.
Customs office?
[noisy]
[Mansik] So
What's going on?
No, they came to the Coast Guard and the Customs Office.
They say they each have their own jurisdiction
I can't even use my hands right now
Baby, no matter what
Where is that? What about the Commissioner?
I'm not receiving any communication
What the Puck!
[Bangbang]
Oh my, they're coming too
- Who?
- Prosecutor
[Seokhyun] Yes
yes, i understand
[noisy]
All stop!
Everything stops!
Ah, this is so annoying, Mr.
This is prosecutor Kim Seok-hyeon.
My younger brother is going between life and death.
The guy called brother
I'm sitting there sucking my butt
[Jaehong] Ah, team leader!
Sergeant Kim was moved to the intensive care unit.
[Beep beep - ECG]
[Jaehong] Luckily
The bullet missed my heart
They say there is no danger to life.
[Mansik] What about consciousness?
[Jaehong] Right now, right after surgery.
They say I have to wait a while.
[Mansik] I can be a teacher
I need to meet you
[Jaehong] Still
Because you taught me how to swim
I found Sergeant Kim.
Inspector Ji had a hard time too.
[Calm music]
But what about Dongju?
[sigh]
[Dongju] ‘2018’?
Is it then?
Uh, where are you going?
He said he wanted to learn boxing.
Sorry, I have somewhere to go.
Oh, when are you coming back?
It won't take long
Then shall we go together?
There is
Uh, okay
[Mansik] Without saying a word
Where have you been, man?
What is that again?
I think I'll have to be hospitalized for a long time
I brought you some things you need.
How is your condition?
Well, not yet
Even if I wake up
I don't know if I can come back
What do you mean?
[Mansik] Sergeant Kim’s ankle is broken
I guess it's not that bad
While playing as a player
I think it was bad
Looks like the fracture is a bit serious this time.
What are you doing? Let’s go. Inspector Ji is alone.
I'll go to the office and come back
Hey, man
[Dongju] Yes?
Are you okay?
It's okay
Well, I'm glad, tsk
[Nurse] Patient, are you conscious?
[Hannah sighs]
Please wait a moment
I'll call you teacher
[Hannah] Yes
Senior, are you okay?
[Hannah sighs]
thank you for waking me up
[Calm music]
[Hannah sighs]
[Dongju] This
[Jaehong] Ah...
What does the commissioner say?
I wasn't making the team
What are you going to do with my subject?
It's all because of my greed
This is what happened
I'm sorry, Inspector Shin.
I have no shame
[Doctor] Wow, you really have no solution.
Mr. Dongju Yoon
[Calm music]
Don't take your situation lightly
After using my body carelessly like this
If your blood pressure suddenly rises
Not only cerebral hemorrhage
By touching the optic nerve
It can even lead to blindness
[Beep - Tinnitus]
[Executive] This case is
Due to excessive investigation by the special investigation team
Police shooting during investigation
This is a place to take responsibility.
While performing a mission
It caused a personnel accident...
[Ding - Ball]
[Audience cheers]
[Jonggu] Well done
[Beep - Tinnitus]
Huh? Foul, foul, foul
time
[Bam!]
[Beep - Tinnitus]
[Referee/English] Break, neutral corner
[Commentator] Nuridin’s
Is it a right hook?
I think I got hit in the elbow.
[Caster] Ah, now it’s Dong-ju Yoon
It looks like my left eye was torn...
[Dongju/Narration] Everything is a mess
[English] Are you okay?
[Dongju’s heavy breathing]
[Dongju/Narration] Damn it
Nothing goes as planned
[Click - Moon]
I'm glad it looks good
I'll be discharged soon
[Jonghyun] Ah, yes
Did you hear about the special teams being disbanded?
If there is a department you want, let me know
The commissioner said he would take care of my convenience.
What about your teammates?
Received suspension and pay reduction
They returned a while ago
[noisy]
- I'm sorry.
- [Woman 1] Oh, let go of this, oppa!
[Mansik] I’m sorry, I’m sorry
You can't do this.
[Woman 1] No...
[Together] Ugh!
[Woman 2] Oh, what is it!
[Woman 1] Where are you touching?
No, I didn't touch it.
You fell asleep
- You touched it!
- [Man-sik] I'm a police officer...
[humorous music]
- [Whoop Whoop - Siren]
- [Woman] Hey, stop the car!
I want to get off, get off!
- Hey, what! Lee, Mr.
- [Mansik] Be quiet.
- Get down!
- Oh, please be quiet!
[Woman] What are you!
[Bibibig - traffic light]
- Stop...
- [Woman] Put me down, put me down
Please stop
Why don't you stop! This is it!
- Hey, save me, save me
- [Woman] Stop anywhere, stop!
Please save me
[Ha! [Sound effect]
[Buzz - Cell Phone]
[Wing - Cell Phone]
[Clears cough]
Tsk
[Police] Where should Hannah be placed immediately?
This is the only place
Other employees also
Hannah looks a little uncomfortable.
Well, if you don't like it, tell me
I'll look elsewhere
It's okay
I’m comfortable alone too
What about Police Officer Yoon?
Oh, that Yun Dong-ju?
He did it by special order from the commissioner.
I'm in a good place
As a special support worker
[Police] Let’s do this quickly.
Because I have to go out in the evening
yes
Then do it together
[Calm music]
[Dongju] Mom, I’m here
I'll clean it for you
It's warm
Kid...
Ah, mother
I didn't know
There are so many good restaurants in Inseong.
Over there in Gumyeon-dong, the kalguksu is delicious.
In Baekdang-dong
The oyster soup is amazing
They say there is a store
Ah, in Jinhang-dong
They say there is a house where Nakgobsae is really delicious.
Mother, do you know what Nakgopsae is?
This is a restaurant that even my mother would really like.
I also go to see flowers
I also went to see the autumn leaves.
It would be nice to go around a lot
[Mansik] Now, due to suspicion of medication.
urine collection
Let's get started quickly
[Joyful music]
[Tingling sound effect]
[Man] Mr.
Can you hold me here?
No, I don't have the strength in my hands.
What do you mean, huh? Not a child
Oh, try to control it, hold it.
Uh, uh, hold it, control it well
[Police] Hurry up!
Hand it over to the drug squad.
you try it
[Man] Oh, really...
- Hey, wait a minute.
- [Man] Oh, yeah
[Mansik] Now, get ready
- [Man] Ah, ah!
- Yes
[Man] Ah, ah!
[Mansik] Hey!
[Click - Moon]
[sigh]
[sniff]
Hey, just wash it off.
Then the shell comes off
- [Mansik] Oh my!
- How many times do you wash it?
[Mansik] Damn druggie
I think I still smell it.
[Dalkkak - Can]
What is it?
[Mansik] Isn’t this old paper?
[Ding sound effect]
Old kimchi in steamed chicken
It suits you well, it's delicious
Right? Isn't it delicious?
- Um
- [Jeong-ah] Dad
Can’t we have a dog?
Oh, what, are you talking bullshit in the middle of the night?
There's even a mutt
It's so annoying I'm dying
- [Interesting Music]
- Mutt, I’m hungry, so come and eat.
I already asked
no
Let's get a puppy, okay?
[Mansik] If you raise it
Who cleans up the poop?
[Jeongah] I can clean it up.
[Mansik] Chiujin, hey
Clean up your room
Is that a room? It's a pig pen
[moktak sound effect]
What are you doing?
Hey, stop spilling, okay?
Did you talk to your mom?
What about school?
Oh, your mom
Why on earth aren't you coming in? huh?
[Growling sound effect]
Eyu
[Bang! - Moon]
[Jeong-ah] That’s what the wind is like!
[Mansik] Fish oil
Hey, where are you going?
Because I'm hungry
I told you to come and eat some of this!
A dog walk
Where did you go on dispatch today?
Support for market events
[Mansik] What about tomorrow?
[Dongju] Intensive crackdown on illegal hoardings
The next day
Is this civic volunteer work at a bank?
Good word, special support workplace
It's not a daily day job.
Baby, it's a fake day
Call me somewhere strange
Making people suffer
It would have been enough if they had suspended me and given me a pay cut.
Oh, wow, what are you doing?
That's right
to a security company
They said there was a spot available
Get a job there at least
This is where my junior does it.
The income won't be worse than it is now.
The hospital bills are not that big, lady.
[Calm music]
Why are you looking at me like that?
Thank you
[snort]
Baby, once again, baby
Why do you care so much?
sorry
Chi, what do I care?
Like a whining mutt
I do that because I'm annoyed
Ah, how pretty is this guy?
When the seasons change, my nose gets really sore.
I'm dying from this pain, huh?
[sigh]
I just then
I should have pretended not to notice
What's so pitiful about this guy?
[Student 1] Hey, where does it hurt?
Come to work
[Student 2] Oh, wait, wait...
Hey, give it up when you tell me to give it up
[Student 3] Are you being beaten by a patient?
[Students groan]
[Dongju] Hey
- [Mansik] Hey, man!
- [Puck!]
Kiyooh, Kiyooh, Kiyooh
[Detective] Fighting at the bottom of character
I guess there was a rumor that he was the best.
So it seems like there are arguments every day.
They say the kid is good
What kind of punch is a good boy, huh?
[Woman] Ayu
I’m an only child so I don’t know anything.
Oh, that guy over there hit me.
[Man-sik] Why isn’t the guardian coming?
[Detective] Oh, it looks like my father doesn’t exist.
My mother isn't answering the phone.
I left my contact information
[Woman] Look at this guy.
Because he hit them all.
[Calm music]
[Dongju’s sobs]
[Dongju] Mom
[Mansik] Oh my, what’s going on?
Looks like I just got hit today
Is this your living room?
Let's see
Now
If you're going to fight, wear that and fight.
Don't fight on the street
Close your eyes, tsk
[Soft music]
[Anchor/TV] Due to doping suspicions
At risk of losing the gold medal
Boxing player Dong-ju Yoon
The results of the Court of Arbitration for Sports
came out
After a two-year long legal battle,
The court ruled against Yoon
The fact that you are taking banned drugs
Saying there wasn't any
Suspension of player eligibility
The result was announced as invalid.
Here is the soccer news
[Mansik clears his throat]
Helping me whenever I was having a hard time
thank you
Thank you
While eating without saying anything dirty
Oh, don't look at me like that.
My handsome face is worn away
Ah, soon I will meet that junior
I'll make an appointment so I know that
Got it?
I'll take care of it.
[Rehabilitation Therapist] Slow down, okay.
one
- Two, slowly.
- [Jonghyun] Huh...
[Rehabilitation Therapist] Hana
Don't push yourself too hard
It's the first day of rehab.
[Jonghyun] Ah
It's not easy, ah...
[Rehabilitation Therapist]
Should we stop here for today?
- [Jonghyun] [Sigh] Yes
- [Rehabilitation Therapist] Okay, let’s go.
[Jonghyun’s moans]
- Yes, thank you for your hard work.
- [Jonghyun] Thank you
[Jonghyun’s labored breathing]
[Hannah] Senior
Do you remember that time?
The day I met my mom before the competition
[sigh]
[Elegant music flows]
[Hannah Mo]
You don’t really like Korean food?
[Man] Western food is good and Korean food is good too.
- I like them all.
- [Hannah Mo] I like everything
Oh my, you're early.
Didn’t Jonghyun come with you? huh?
[Hannah] Did you call your senior?
Oh, I told you we broke up.
[Hannah Mo]
Even if we break up, we can meet again
How common are kids like Jonghyun?
[Hannah sighs]
Mom will take care of it.
Oh, this guy comes to this place.
Come decorate it a little
But who is it?
Hey, sit down
[Man] Is that so?
- [Hannah Mo] To be shy
- [Man] Ah
- hi
- Did you tell me? That person from last time
[Man] Better than what I saw on TV
The real thing is much better
This is Richard Jeong.
[sigh]
[Hannah Mo] Okay, that’s enough
The tie pin is pretty.
This? It’s pretty, right?
This is an important day today
my darling
Lee gave it to me as a gift.
I bought that
Really?
thank you
Because you're training, huh?
I would be out of my mind and out of time.
When did you prepare for this?
[snort]
When I was 12
then
national sports festival
I bought it with the winning prize money.
As a birthday present for my father who passed away
[Hannah Mo] Ah...
So you don't have to be thankful.
Because it’s not yours
Ha...
- Mr.
- [Hannah Mo] Oh my
- Oh my, ah...
- [Richard] Baby
- [groan]
- [Hannah Mo] Oh, I’m so sorry.
- The kid is a little sensitive right now.
- [Beep - Tinnitus]
- [Hannah] Ah!
- [Wudangtang]
sorry
[heavy music]
It's Hannah
Ah...
- Ah!
- [Meaningful sound effects]
[Beep - Tinnitus]
[Bam!]
- Are you okay?
- Yes
[heavy music]
I said it was okay
So that's it? game that day
[Knock knock knock]
yes
[Staff] Are you ready?
[Audience cheers]
[Caster] On the ankle
What's the problem?
Today, Kim Jong-hyun
I can't move forward.
[Hannah] Why didn’t you tell me?
Then I'm so sorry
I should have told you
Yeah, I should have said that.
Then our relationship
Has it changed?
I wanted to start over, back then
i still
I want to start again with you
Why isn't your sister coming?
[Bang!]
[Mansik] If you get into trouble, just stop.
Do you have any regrets about the police?
Are you stuck?
[Wing - Cell Phone]
[Jonghyun] I still
I want to start again with you
But this is just my heart
never to you
I don't want to burden you
And because of that
I didn't lose the game
So don't worry too much
[cell phone notification sound]
[Korea Customs Service Employee 1]
Manager, you need to say something.
[Chief] Huh?
Oh, me? A, ai, ai
[Korea Customs Service Employee 1] Oh, what are you doing?
quickly, quickly, quickly
Uh, okay, I guess so? Um, hmm
Uh, in the meantime, Director Min.
As a Korean member of our Korea Customs Service,
It was hard, yeah
Oh, I heard you’re retiring like this.
Too bad, uh
It's been a long time, yeah
- Thank you for your hard work, Manager.
- [Chief] Oh, yeah
I'll contact you often, yes
Huh?
Uh, uh, yes, yes, yes
Now, now, now, now, now, let's have a drink
[together] yes
salty
[Korea Customs Service Employee 2]
If you look closely, Jooyoung
I don't drink, I don't smoke
I don't even have a lover
No, what do you do for fun?
[Korea Customs Service Employee 1] I’m curious.
Right, Chief?
[Chief] Huh?
Uh, sure
What fun should I have? Yeah
[Laughter from customs officials]
I'm having more fun living than I thought
[Yuna] As I wish
You can choose them all, then?
[Jooyoung] Of course
- Then I will choose.
- [Jooyoung] Yes
[Yuna] What should I do?
[Rattle - Bell]
[Flower Shop Owner] Hello
[Guest] Yes
[Small] Do you think it's fun?
[Nervous music]
What happened without any contact?
- [Flower Shop Owner] Can I help you?
- [Devil] No
Are we in contact and seeing each other?
sadly
That kid
Are you just leaving it at that?
the police
A mutt who doesn't listen
I need to tie it up nearby.
And it's as cute as you say
Everything is folding up and down
Did you come to ask that?
[The devil sighs]
I need to let you know when the work is done.
Where are you? That bitch
Why are you so impatient?
where is it
Do you really know?
If you fooled me
It'll be hard to handle
[Jooyoung] Then
how could i lie about that
What I remember is you
It's just him
a gift to work hard
we'll see each other soon
If I make all the candy,
[Child] Go first
My sister will definitely pick you up.
[Devil] Then, sister
until we meet again
My sister, please keep this pin.
promise
[Child] Yes, I promise
By all means
[Rattle - Door]
[Hannah Mo] Oh! It's hot, it's hot
Why is the day like this?
[Hannah] Why are you so late?
[Hannah Mo] Why like this?
I don't know if there's traffic
Hey, check this out, huh?
I brought this from Jochiwon
It's a peach
Big and sweet crab
The taste is so amazing
It's really hard to get this, huh?
Look, what it looks like
It looks pretty like a baby’s bottom, right?
Take a whiff, it's very sweet...
Ah, that's enough
But why peaches all of a sudden?
You hate dad
No, what does your dad hate?
Why are you wearing that?
Uh, is there something happening today?
mom
You don’t know what day it is today, do you?
today? What day is it?
huh?
Oh my, my, uh, uh, oh my
Uh, what is it?
her!
- Oh my.
- [Click - Moon]
Hey, come with me, Hannah!
[Meaningful music]
[Devil] Wow, that’s a good drink.
[Leo] Sorry
Because this belongs to someone else
[Seokhyun] Ha... I finished the discharge process.
Why are there so many things to sign?
Come and go
Bloodlines are so annoying
I've never called you bro
[Seokhyun] Hey, me too
Did you come because you missed me?
Because of you and that great special team
How much work has piled up at the prosecutor's office?
you and this time
What if it's really wrong, Mr.
You're worried
my father
I'm not a kid
father at this age
Running errands
What are you doing?
[Calm music]
What my father said
If you're going to keep doing this nonsense
He wants you to hand over all your shares to me.
You know your father’s personality better, right?
I became a police officer and got shot.
You really can't stand it anymore
Once you decide, send it through Secretary Kim.
Hey
If you want to hide, hide properly
If you want to fight, fight right
These are empty words, but
Take good care of yourself
[Roaring - door]
[Ding Dong]
[Dongju] Ah, welcome
[Voice guidance] Welcome
Welcome
- [Dongju] Welcome
- [Ding Dong]
- Yes, welcome.
- [Beep]
[Voice guidance] Welcome
[dark music]
[Jooyoung] Thank you
Thanks to you, I received severance pay.
I got some savings
If you’re thankful, you can buy me some food
Is that so?
What do you want to eat?
Ha, indeed
Enjoy your meal
[Dongju] Is this all you’re buying me?
I'm unemployed, so now I have to save money too.
Prices have risen a lot too.
Chi, you have a very clear sense of economics.
No, if it’s a waste, eat alone, why?
[Jooyoung] It seems like you don’t have any friends either.
It's good to eat together with people who don't have one.
[Meaningful music]
[Leo] Sorry
Because this belongs to someone else
[Chief of Police] That’s a black cat.
Active in the Russian Far East
They say it was a mafia organization.
[Pawnshop owner] It used to be very famous.
There was a smuggler
It's called Ottala
that person
Where can I meet you?
It was blowing to death
Has it been 15 years?
[Hannah] In Inseong City in 2008
the russian mafia
There was an incident where he was shot and killed.
Ouch!
[Child 1] Hey, don’t follow me.
It's embarrassing
[Child 2] Until both feet ride
You can't play with us.
play with babies
[Dongju] Huh? Those kids are really
[Calm music]
Ah...
[Click - Moon]
[Police] What are you doing?
Are you a detective?
Are you bored?
No, I didn't do what I was told.
Are you playing with something like this?
why? What this time
Dealing with the Russian mafia?
sorry
Why are there ranks and departments?
Ms. Hanna
Hannah's job is organizing the warehouse.
To catch these criminals quickly
It's best to stick to your job, tsk
It would be better to start from area B.
Hurry up, or else
They say it will be disposed of within a month.
yes
[Police] Icham
[Police laugh]
[Meaningful music]
[Police] Hello
This is the Investigation Support Department of the Inseong Police Agency.
yes, nice to meet you
Um, on today's live broadcast
Many people participated
Thank you very much
Your dream is to become a police officer...
[Pawnshop owner] Oh Bong-chan
This guy took money and started a business.
I earned a lot of money.
I drew it and got the name wrong.
[Hannah] 'Due to a gunshot wound to the head
'Presumed dead'
'30 caliber Russian made
'Estimated Tokarev'
[Ding Dong]
[Jooyoung] Why?
Let's fight some more?
Stop it now
Do you think your tenacity is pretty good?
I'm pretty used to brawls
I grew up getting beaten so much
Eat a lot and come to your senses now
You're saying that because I'm like your younger brother.
No matter how much you struggle alone
Nothing changes
What do people move by?
- Still don't know?
- [Gurgling - Counter]
[Voice guidance] Welcome
[Jooyoung] Stop it now
No matter how much you struggle alone
Nothing changes
[Notification sound]
[wing]
[cell phone notification sound]
[Jinsu’s son] Huh?
Why don't you ride a bike?
Is it broken?
Kids are making fun of me
baby rides a bike
Dad decided to take it off for me.
Teach me to ride a bike
[Dongju] Now
[clatter rattle]
[Jinsu's son] Do you know how to do it?
Oh well, of course
Just wait a moment
It'll be done soon
- Mr.
- [Dongju] Huh?
Aren’t we going to catch bad people anymore?
uh?
Uh...
Oh, that's not it
I have a moment.
[Jinsu’s son] Then
Dad, who made it like that?
[Heo Seong-jin, Diori’s ‘Night of Counting Stars’]
What?
[Jinsu’s son] Grandma said that.
Dad, the person who made it like that
It's not him
I haven't caught it yet
[clatter rattle]
Done
Do you want to take a ride?
Can I ride this alone?
Well, you can ride alone too.
I learned it on my own too
Why?
There was no one to teach me
[Dongjubu] Wake up
- Wake up! Sigh, let go
- [Rudang!]
[Mija] Hey, Dongju’s dad!
- [Dongjubu] Do you want to die?
- [Mija] Ah, Dongju’s father
Why are you hitting your sick wife? Why!
[Jinsu's son] What if I fall?
If you fall, just get up
Clench your teeth
If you avoid it because you're scared, you can't do anything.
[sigh]
I'll hold you from behind, so don't be scared.
I can do it
And my dad is the one who made it like that
I will definitely catch it
I promise
If you say something, you're the kind of person who does it.
look ahead
I'm not letting go, I'm not letting go
Okay, let's go.
Oh, it's a good ride, it's a good ride
Hold on, man hold on
- [Puck!]
- [Intense music]
[cell phone notification sound]
[Man's scream]
Let go, let go!
Ah, ah, ah!
[Man's scream]
[cell phone notification sound]
[Man] Why are you doing that?
Come on, man!
[tick tock]
[Mobile phone notification sound]
[Man's groan]
[tick tock]
[Man] Are you here?
What is this?
[Man] Oh, that’s it, Mr.
Ah, what kind of guy is that?
Suddenly came and brought...
[noisy]
Come!
- [Mart Employee 1] Come quickly!
- [Mart Employee 2] Oh, sir!
[intense music]
[Mart owner] That bastard just
Catch it and kill it
[Mart Employee 1] Oh my!
[Mart Employee 2] You bastard!
Hey, wake up
Hey, grab it this way!
Get it!
[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]
[Mart owner] Huh?
Hey, hey, hey... uh!
- [Mart owner] Oh, really!
- Bow down.
[Mart owner] Oh! Wait a minute
Uh, help me, I was wrong.
Save me!
Ah, ah, ah, Mr.
Kid! you bastard
Did President Kim send you this?
Or boss Oh?
you bastard
Whose store is this?
I'm doing this because I know
Why on earth are you doing this?
tell me one name
- That's all.
-Whose name?
Yo
- [Somber Music]
- [ticking]
[Dongju] This
Who else is there?
[Mart owner] Here.
Please take it out of here
Ah, yes
Oh, yes, please take this away.
Yes, thank you, ah
Oh, thank you, thank you.
[Police] Let’s put on the handcuffs.
No, handcuffs
Can I kick it later?
[Reporter/TV] Recently operated illegally
About business places
Suspension of business and closure of business premises, etc.
Disposition has been issued
All of these were reported by a citizen.
I got caught.
The reporter was in the CCTV
As a man
It is estimated
- The man believed to be the reporter in the video
- [Jaehong] Huh?
[Reporter/TV] Cover your face with a hoodie
I don't know the exact identity, but
Recently reported
CCTV footage from illegal business establishments...
- [Man] Oh!
-You bastard! I, I...
[Man] Ah, Mr...
No, not the boss.
That bastard, that one
[Man-sik] To the police
Do you have any regrets about sticking with it?
[Dongju] The only thing I’m proud of in my life
Gold medal and police officer
I won't lose it to anyone
Until I catch that bastard
never
[tick tock]
[Sharp sound effect]
The moment you get scared, that's where it ends
If you want to hide, hide properly
If you want to fight, fight right
[Voice guidance] I can't answer the phone.
To the sound source...
[Call end sound]
[Beep]
[Exciting music]
[Dongju/Narration]
Between rounds
1 minute short time
That time
Just quench your thirst
It's not time to wipe your sweat
To win the next round
It's time to hunker down.
"Justice"
- [Ding - Ball]
- [Jonggu] Let’s go!
[tick tock]
child, Mr.
It's a bit much
[Man] What?
What are you doing you bastard?
[MAX's 'GET IN THE RING']
[Dongju/Narration]
The game was only paused for a moment.
[Man] Hey, hit it!
[Dongju/Narration] The round is
It's not over yet
[Hannah] Hey, why do you keep avoiding me?
[Forensic Supervisor] Is the time okay?
I have something to show you briefly.
I haven't come home for several days.
What on earth are you doing?
[People's screams]
[Jonghyun] Minjooyoung replaces
How much money do you have?
[Seokchun] The devil knows about Enna
What should I do?
Is it because of the person you are looking for?
- [Devil] Yes
- [Mansik] In the stabbing
Even if the police get shot, it's quiet
From above
I'm going to crush you with my butt!
[Gold Rabbit] He will know
Where did Min Joo-young hide the money?
Hey, 4889
[Jooyoung] Have you eaten?
If you didn't eat, should we do it together?
You have no choice but to avoid it
[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]